紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   煮粥達人
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   WalkingNerd
翻譯   鹽湖涼開水
時間軸   大蔥
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第五集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
總統在哪里
馬修·道得
ABC新聞政治分析家
斯蒂芬妮·庫特
民主黨參謀
悲傷統帥
總統在逃避什么
圣達菲警局
謝潑德自由基金會
民主在運作
國防部長稱總統無視高級顧問
聯調局調查副總統與俄羅斯勾結的指控
她什么時候過世的
What time did she die?
我不...
I don't...
抱歉  我知道這么問不合適
Sorry, I know it's a weird question.
如果不是他  那么
If it's not him, then...
她到底是怎么死的
how did she die, for God's sake?
你認為凱茜到底發生什么了
What do you think really happened to Cathy?
你大概是運氣好吧
I guess you got lucky then.
沒人運氣那么好
No one is that lucky.
敘利亞問題的談判破裂了  他來干什么
The talks on Syria have broken down, what's he doing here?
如果我們無所作為
If we do nothing,
亂局就會繼續擴大
the chaos will continue.
那么我的條件如下
So, here's what I want.
俄羅斯獨占所有近海石油和天然氣開發
Russian exclusivity on all offshore oil and gas exploration.
她什么都沒說
And she said nothing.
你怎么不告訴他們是我邀請你來的呢
Why didn't you tell them I invited you?
有關投標將經過我的批準
Bids will be contingent on my approval.
油氣和港口可以都歸你
You can have the oil and gas, the ports.
以及轉運資源利潤的20%
And 20% of profits from the resources passing through.
我接受
I accept.
瑞秋·波斯納
Rachel Posner?
有人頂著她的名頭
Somebody with her name
在新墨西哥到處消費
is bouncing checks in and around New Mexico.
你和克萊爾是怎么回事
What's going on with you and Claire?
科爾議員  我讓他跟我一起競選2020
Congressman Cole. I'll put him on my ticket 2020.
那你也得赦免弗蘭西斯
Pardon Francis as well.
那關于弗蘭西斯的遺囑  有件事你應該知道
There is something that you should know about Francis' will.
他留給你的可不止兩個袖扣
He left you more than those cuff links.
-你好  卡儂妮卡  -克萊爾  你在干什么
- Good day, Calonice. - Claire, what are you doing?
想事情
Thinking.
你現在應該上臺了
You're supposed to be on-stage right now.
卡儂妮卡  我受不了了
"Calonice, it's more than I can bear.
滿腦子想著性事  燥熱得不行
I am hot all over with blushes for our sex.
男人們說我們是狡猾的流氓
Men say we're slippery rogues..."
他們說得不對嗎
"And aren't they right?"
走吧  我們走
Come on, let's go.
走啊
Come on.
我們早晚都會死
We're all gonna die one day.
什么
What?
我會死
I'm gonna be dead,
你會死
you're gonna be dead.
他們都會死
They're all gonna be dead.
所有人
Everybody.
你究竟在說什么
What the fuck are you talking about?
那是我的耳環嗎
Are those my earrings?
我以為你不會介意
I... didn't think you'd care.
你去吧
You do it.
《利西翠妲》是古希臘早期喜劇作家
阿里斯多芬尼斯的作品
講述利西翠妲鼓動交戰城邦的女性"性罷工"
以結束戰爭
你來演利西翠妲  臺詞你都知道  對吧
You be Lysistrata. You know all my lines, right?
你不能就
You can't just--
演出怎么辦  克萊爾
What about the show? Claire!
我們就快好了  得再調一下燈光
We are almost good. We just have to adjust the lights.
沒關系
That's fine.
我非常感謝您來參加訪談
I did want to thank you personally for doing this.
我真的很感激
I really appreciate it.
等我們完事后再謝吧
Wait till we're finished before you do that.
我不會問不該問的問題
Well, I won't deviate from the questions.
你什么都可以問  只要是與
You can ask me anything, as long as it's about the...
總統有關的
the president.
-能別給我弄那個嗎  -抱歉
- Can you get away from me with that? - My apologies.
-這樣就行了  -抱歉  謝潑德先生
- I'm fine. - Sorry, Mr. Shepherd.
化妝是因為光非常亮
It's just that the lights are pretty harsh.
沒事  開始吧
It's fine. Let's go.
俄羅斯霸權條款
This Russia debacle,
基本上就是向
it's essentially a 20% tax
去該地區幫忙的美國公司
on American companies that are just over there
收取20%的稅
trying to help out the region.
這是本屆政府近來
It's the latest in a series of...
頻頻做出的災難決策的最新一條
disastrous steps taken by this White House.
就難怪
And you wonder--
難怪國會要立法
You wonder why Congress was looking at legislation
拿走她的核武公文包
to take the nuclear button away from her.
作為一名愛國者
As a patriot,
作為一名熱愛祖國和自己公司的美國人
as an American who loves his country and, yes, his company,
我們可以做得更好
we can do better.
我們可以做得遠比現在好
We can do so much better.
就連比爾·謝潑德
Even Bill Shepherd,
他以前從不接受采訪
who the last time he was interviewed on air was never--
就連他都感到非發聲不可了
Even he felt compelled to speak out.
她是我黨首腦  我得說我感到困惑
She's the head of my party, and I have to say, I'm at a loss.
她的整個日程都是空的
Her entire schedule is empty.
以前也有總統失蹤
Presidents have gone missing before--
但是在戴維營清理思緒
But there's a difference between clearing your head at Camp David
有嚴重強迫癥的天才大亨
可參見電影《飛行家》
和跟霍華德·休斯一樣閉門不出不是一回事
and going full-blown Howard Hughes.
她已經三周沒有公開露面  也沒有任何消息
She hasn't been seen publicly in three weeks or heard from.
除了某日半夜赦免了她丈夫的幕僚長
Except for a late night pardon for her husband's chief of staff.
而很多人認為這是個戰略錯誤
Which many consider a strategic mistake.
道格·斯坦普是有問題的
Well, Doug Stamper has issues.
她政府的每個人都有問題
Everyone in her administration has issues.
新聞發言人肖恩·杰弗瑞斯辭職了
Sean Jeffries, the press secretary, has resigned.
可能還會有更多人離任
And there are probably more departures to come.
她的內閣已經受夠了
Her cabinet has had enough.
如果她認為一次赦免就能擺脫聯邦檢察官
And if she thinks a pardon is gonna keep the US Attorney away,
-她可就...  -她
- she's-- - She's--
-抑郁了  -我說不好是不是抑郁
- Depressed. - I don't know about depressed.
她看上去不是精神失常就是很抑郁
You know, she looks either very disturbed, or depressed.
但是  精神失常  能那樣說嗎
But, I mean, "disturbed"? Can you really say that?
是的  等等
Yeah. Look, hold on.
我對她的領導能力有很大的疑問
I'm asking a very real question about her ability to lead here.
你們見過這張照片嗎  我們見過
Have you seen this photo? Because we have.
我們不想妄下診斷
Now we're not here to diagnose,
但你看到這張照片  肯定會心生懷疑
but you look at this, and you need to ask.
從國家的角度來講
On behalf of our country,
那個女人讓我們的外交政策倒退了30年
that woman undid 30 years of foreign policy
她表現得像個  原諒我說臟話  像個[慫包]
by acting like, pardon my French, a...
但是現在  我們進入了一個新階段
But now, now we're into a new phase.
白宮燈火輝煌  卻無人坐鎮
When the White House lights are on, but nobody's home.
她倒是在里面  但不肯出來
I mean, she's home, but she won't leave.
已經縮在那里23天了  還沒有要出來的意思
Been hunkered down in there for 23 days and counting.
顯然  她已經停止工作了
Apparently, she's stopped doing anything.
她癱瘓了
She's paralyzed.
一個癱瘓的[臭娘們]
A paralyzed...
而最危險的就是一個癱瘓的[臭娘們]
And there's nothing more dangerous than a paralyzed...
說真的  我覺得她可能是有史以來
Seriously, I think she might be the worst thing
這個國家最糟糕的災難
that has ever happened to this country.
緊急求救
SOS.
救救我們的靈魂  救救我們的大船
Save our souls, save our ships,
這兩個說法都合適
Take your pick.
這可不是鬧著玩的
This ... is real.
我是梅樂蒂·科魯茲  這就是我的評論
I'm Melody Cruz, and that's what I got.
那張抓拍真不錯  是不是
That's quite a snapshot, right?
獨一無二  精心設計過
Unique. Carefully calibrated.
痛苦  歇斯底里再加一點點瘋狂
Pain, hysteria and just a small dose of crazy.
他們從未見過這樣的克萊爾·安德伍德
Claire Underwood, like they've never seen before.
其實沒有看上去那么簡單
It's actually not as easy as it looks.
要擺出那樣的表情
See, in order for me to make that face,
我得發揮想象
I have to imagine...
把各種情緒完美糅合到一起
the perfect combination of things.
配方如下
Here's the recipe.
首先  我得想著
First, I have to think about all the ways
我這一生中  男人操控我的各種辦法
in which men have tried to manage me my whole life.
然后  我要想到
Then, I think of...
美國民眾最擔心的事
America's worst fear...
就一個女人坐進總統辦公室而言
when it comes to a female in the Oval Office.
-她的日程全推干凈了  -最后
- Her schedule has been cleared. - And finally...
我最后悔的事  弗蘭西斯·J·安德伍德
...my biggest regret-- Francis J. Underwood.
總統女士
Madam President.
你病了嗎
Are you ill?
要是病了  我去請白宮醫生
If you're ill, I'll call the White House physician.
克萊爾
Claire.
出去  馬克
Just get out, Mark.
克萊爾  不能再這樣下去了
Claire, this has to stop.
請讓我一個人靜靜
Please, just leave me alone.
你引發了全國性的恐慌  你得振作起來
You are alarming the nation. You need to get up.
聽著
Listen.
我準備了一段簡短的聲明
I've prepared a short statement
解釋你之前為何不露面  并宣布回歸
explaining your absence and announcing your return.
你可以今天下午在玫瑰園發表聲明
You can deliver it in the Rose Garden this afternoon.
這是為了我們好
I promise you this is for both of our sakes.
你不明白
You don't understand...
請先回避
If you would, please.
克萊爾
Claire...
看著我
look at me.
-看著我  -出去
- Look at me. - Get out.
出去吧
Please get out.
-別管我  -你這樣不僅是自掘墳墓
- Just leave me alone. - You are not only digging your own grave,
還在葬送你的總統職位  別再這樣了
you are burying the presidency. Stop it.
你努努力
You can try.
-努努力好嗎  -不行  馬克
- Can you try? - I can't, Mark.
我做不到
I just can't.
I can't.
別擔心
Don't worry.
我有計劃
I have a plan.
抱歉
Excuse me.
先生
Sir.
沒問題吧
We're good here?
好  謝謝
Yeah. Thank you.
是多疑還是應當
Was it paranoia or is it due diligence?
你說呢  馬克
You tell me, Mark.
我們剛剛見識了這個賤人多有能耐
We both just lived through what that bitch is capable of.
肯定是出了什么問題
Something is definitely wrong.
她...
She...
喝咖啡嗎
Coffee?
她連說話都缺乏條理
I mean, she can't even put two sentences together.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
我從來沒見過她這樣  她一團亂
I've never seen her like this. She's a mess.
那么
Well...
不管怎樣  這改變不了我們的處境
Either way, that doesn't change where we are.
還有  馬克
And, Mark...
康威垮掉后
when Conway imploded,
我們發現你有些
we recognized that you were a little squea--
太過謹慎  沒有立即上位
squeamish about stepping in.
我們很欣賞這一點
And we appreciate that.
但現在是時候了
But it's time.
你會成為一個偉大的總統的
You'll make a great president.
我們會確保的
We'll see to that.
等等  我們把話說明白
Now, wait, wait. Let's be clear, okay?
我知道我們一直在狠狠打壓她
I know we've been hitting her pretty hard,
但我不能允許再對她下一次手
but I can't condone another attempt.
-我做不到  -冷靜
- I can't. - Calm down.
天啊  馬克  說真的
My God, Mark. I mean, really.
還有其他辦法
There are other ways.
好  我們是要彈劾她
Okay, so we're talking about impeachment
還是國會政府
or a congressional government?
第25修正案第四款
25th Amendment, Section 4.
從來沒人用過
Which has never been used.
是為了迅速扼殺信心危機
It's built for speed, intended to smother a crisis of confidence.
讓民眾安心
Reassure the public.
讓世界安心
Reassure the world
美國政府還能繼續運作
that continuity remains at the American government,
就算總統變得...
even if a president becomes...
-無法履行他的職責  -她的職責
- Unable to fulfill his duties. - Her duties.
-前提是她無法勝任  -她現在確實無法勝任
- It requires her to be unfit. - And she is.
而且
I mean...
我們的律師已經查過了
our lawyers have already looked into this.
她只要能力不足就行
She only needs to be deficient.
法律寫得模棱兩可  可以變通
The language is vague and accommodating.
馬克  如果你對此
Mark, if you have any doubt about this
-有所顧慮  -繼續說
- at all-- - I'm just listening.
內閣聽命于你
The Cabinet is yours.
你在參眾兩院都有關系
You have relationships inside the Senate, the House,
兩黨也都有人脈
on both sides of the aisle.
非常合適
It's a natural fit.
但這事必須做得
But the thing has to cascade with--
天衣無縫
Precision.
先由副總統和內閣多數成員
A chain reaction beginning with a letter to Congress,
聯名寫信給國會
signed by the vice president
建議彈劾我
and a majority of his Cabinet,
然后形成連鎖反應
recommending my removal from office.
我怎么會猜到他們的招數
And how do I know that's what they'll try to do?
因為第25條就是沖我來的
Because the 25th gets personal.
比爾喜歡我做落難少女
Bill likes me being the damsel in distress.
想得美吧
He wishes I were.
你去哪兒
Where you headed?
我在北方有家人
I have family up north.
哪兒
Where?
北方
North.
凱茜的姐姐還在科德角嗎
Cathy's sister still on the Cape?
在海恩尼斯  是吧
Hyannis, right?
很好
It's good.
家人很重要
Family's important.
尤其是在艱難時刻
Especially during trying times--
我也想請你進來  但我真的...
I'd invite you in, but I really--
有些事我總想不通
There's still something that I can't get straight.
你再跟我說一遍吧  當時
If we could go through it one more time. So...
她被一輛車接去醫生那兒
She was picked up by car to be taken to the doctor.
她不太舒服
She wasn't feeling well.
直到她發生栓塞前你一直跟她在一起
You were with her the whole time leading up to the embolism?
斯坦普先生  夠了
Mr. Stamper, enough!
我只想弄清怎么回事
I'm just trying to understand what happened.
你別再來纏著我了
I don't need you coming around here anymore.
你清楚是怎么一回事
You know exactly what happened.
也知道驗尸結果  事情就是這樣
You have the coroner's conclusions. And that's that.
我還在哀悼我妻子
I'm in mourning for my wife,
我不想再提起她生命的最后時刻
and I'm not reliving the final moments of her life anymore.
不想跟你提
Not with you.
我覺得你妻子是被謀殺的
I think your wife was murdered.
我要關門了
I'm closing the door now.
-喂  -道格  我是弗萊德·安博格
- Hello. - Doug. Fred Amburg here.
-這是誰的電話  -我的
- Whose phone is this? - This one's mine.
我剛出來
I just got out.
我才知道
I had no idea.
我今早還跟科爾通過話
I talked to Cole this morning.
我聽說了件我們那位心理醫生的事
Heard an interesting thing about our esteemed shrink.
他休假了  事假
You know, that sabbatical, leave,
去旅行了  隨你怎么說
walkabout, whatever you want to call it.
你在找他  是吧
You are looking for him, aren't you?
對
Yes.
他在弗吉尼亞州的一間小屋
He's in a cabin down in Virginia.
給
Here you go.
我可以...
Would you mind if I...?
謝謝
Thanks.
喂
Oh, hello?
別說話  別開口  等著
Don't say another word. Don't speak. Just wait.
抱歉  我拐錯彎  跑進樓梯井了
My apologies, I took a wrong turn and wound up in some stairwell.
我們時間不多  得趕回樓上
We don't have much time until we have to get back upstairs.
瑪茜最初跟我提這個想法時
When Marcy first came to me with this proposition,
豪不夸張地說  我震驚了
I was stunned, to say the least.
直到近來
Until recently I--
我才...我沒想到事情會這么糟
I don't know. I didn't realize how truly bad things were.
但趕總統下臺  我的天啊
But unseat the president? Jesus Christ.
總統是我的朋友
President's my friend.
雖說我擔心她的精神狀況
And while I worry about her mental state,
但我更擔心國家的狀況
I worry about the state of this nation more.
副總統先生  我很敬佩你
Mr. Vice President, I admire you greatly.
但我不習慣做這種事
But I'm not used to this kind of thing.
背地里謀算
Back rooms, after hours.
我們得一萬個小心
We need to take every precaution.
光是過來就很危險了
And yet we're still at risk just by being here.
抱歉
I'm sorry,
但我相信總統一職的神圣性
but I believe in the sanctity of the office of the presidency.
所以我們才聚在這里
And that's exactly why we're here.
你這是讓我們背棄誓言
You're asking us to betray an oath.
我是讓大家吐露心聲
I'm asking you to speak your mind.
這里的每個人齊心協力
A concentrated effort, all of us in this room.
我們或許救不了總統
We may not be able to save the president,
但或許救得了我們的政府
but we may just be able to save our administration.
第25條不僅要看準時機
The 25th is not just about timing.
還要絕對保密
It's about secrecy.
參議院一向守不住秘密
And the Senate hasn't kept a secret--
厄爾  感謝你提到這一點
Earl, I appreciate that.
眾議院已在我掌控之中  參議院也交給我
I have the House, and I'll take care of the Senate.
我會起草一封信
I'll prepare a letter
詳細列出總統的瀆職
detailing the president's dereliction of duty,
向國會和后世解釋清楚
laying out a case for Congress and for posterity.
等時機成熟  就會通知大家
And when the time comes, you'll all be notified.
我們都是愛國者
Look, we're all patriots here.
我們最牽掛的  我們唯一牽掛的  必須是
Our first concern, our only concern, has got to be...
國家的生死存亡
the survival of our nation.
該死
Fuck!
坐下吧  深呼吸
Sit and take a deep breath.
坐下
Sit down.
羅森醫生  坐下
Dr. Rosen, sit down.
你怎么進來的
How did you get in here?
我想  你在這兒是因為你很痛苦
I'm assuming you're here because you're suffering.
如果不是為佐伊·巴恩斯
And if it's not over Zoe Barnes,
就是為另一個被你毀掉的人
it's over some other soul that you've torn apart.
不對
No.
你想  我在這兒
You're assuming I'm here
是因為我發現了你拿走了我什么東西
because I figured out what you took from me.
-拿走  -沒給我
- Took? - Kept.
所有個人物品都應該在出院時歸還原主
All personal property should have been returned upon release.
你說得對  是應該
You're right. It should have.
專業人士竟然做出這種事
There's no accounting for the behavior of supposed professionals.
我曾經在社交場合遇到過一個心理醫生
I once met this psychologist, socially,
她跟我說
who told me about
她曾經給同僚們辦了一次派對
a party that she hosted once for a group of her peers.
請了一屋子的心理醫生
It was just a roomful of shrinks.
那晚派對結束后  她在打掃
At the end of the night, she was cleaning up,
走進衛生間
she went into the bathroom
發現她的某個同事把屎
and she saw that one of her colleagues had smeared shit
糊了一墻
all over the bathroom wall.
什么變態會做出那種事
Now, what kind of fucked up person would do something like that?
看來傳言是真的
Well, I guess it's true what they say.
心理醫生才是最變態的
That shrinks are the most fucked up of all.
那種行為很是暴力
Such a violence to that act.
但暴力很有趣
But violence is a funny thing.
其實受害者記得最清楚的
You know, it's not so much the physical pain
不是肉體上的疼痛
that can victims can remember.
而是當時的感覺
It's the feelings around it.
那種恐懼
The fear.
在哪  你扣下的遺囑在哪  你放哪了
Where is it? The will you intercepted? Where is it?
已經不在我這兒了
I don't have it anymore.
不在我這兒
I don't have it!
里面寫了什么
What was in it?
他把一切都留給了你
He left you everything.
天啊
God...
拿著吧
Take it.
謝謝
Thank you.
我當時就覺得那么問很奇怪
I thought it was a strange question.
什么
What?
你問我弗蘭西斯·安德伍德留給我什么了
When you asked me what Francis Underwood had given me.
遺囑的結語就是這樣的
That's how the will ends.
"記住我最后給你的那樣東西"
"Remember the last thing I gave you."
別給她打電話  否則我會回來的
Don't call her or I'll be back.
希望你能搞清楚自己的問題  醫生
Hope you figure out your problems, Doctor.
拿走吧
Take it.
想要的話  就送你了
If you want it, it's yours.
你想沒想過  自己過的是別人的生活
Do you ever wonder if you're living somebody else's life?
你過的是誰的生活  簡
Whose life are you living, Jane?
我在問你呢
Not me. You.
你好像飽受身份困擾
You seem to be struggling with your identity.
希望這樣說現任總統不會太...
If that's not too impertinent to say to a...
冒昧
sitting president.
過來陪我換睡衣吧
Come keep me company while I put my jammies on.
幫我一下
Please.
你在葬禮上佯裝順從
Your little show of compliance at the funeral
卻和維克多私下達成協議
as you made your side deal with Victor.
讓我不禁想
Makes me wonder.
現在呢
And now what?
你現在演的是哪一出
What do you call this show?
怎樣在短短三周內讓三億兩千三百萬人都反對你
How to turn 323 million people against you in three short weeks?
恭喜  克萊爾
Congratulations, Claire.
你現在讓所有人頭疼
You've become a problem for everybody.
還有
And...
你要知道
Just so you know,
敘利亞可能無可挽回了
Syria may be too far gone.
告訴我該怎么辦  簡
Tell me what to do, Jane.
我今晚參加了一個活動
I was at an event tonight.
通常  總統都會參加
An event the president usually attends.
今晚過得如何
And how was that evening?
正在形成的風暴很難對付
The storm that's gathering is a rough one.
你覺得他們什么時候會動手
When you think they'll strike?
我不知道
I have no idea.
有點晚了
It's late.
我正是這意思
That's exactly what I'm saying.
我想我該搬出去了
I think I should move out.
我理解
I understand.
你再這么下去  總統女士
Stick to this course, Madam President,
那么...
and...
座無虛席呢
Full house.
你們想必是想聽不同的答案
You must be looking for different answers
這相同的問題已經問了...
to the same questions we've been going over for the last--
24天
Now, 24 days.
而總統仍然沒離開官邸
And the president still hasn't left the residence.
-我只能說...  -凱爾茜  拜托
- And this is where I say-- - Kelsey, come on.
目前  與俄羅斯所達成的旨在維系
For now, the ground-breaking accord with Russia,
敘利亞公正且持久的和平的突破性協議
which aims for a just and lasting peace in Syria,
就足以說明一切
speaks for itself.
那么
So,
除非各位還有其他問題
unless there are any more questions,
應該說新的問題  請說
or shall I say new questions? Yes.
真正操盤的人是不是副總統
Isn't the vice president really the one running the show,
實質上掌控了總統實權
essentially acting as president?
有些內閣成員也這么說
There are members of the cabinet who are saying as much.
首先  提及白宮事宜時
Well, firstly, I would refrain from using the word "show,"
不建議使用"操盤"這種字眼
when it comes to the White House.
那么  今天就到此結束
And-- yeah. That's all for today.
謝謝
Thank you.
你確定不餓嗎
Are you sure you're not hungry?
湯還不錯
The soup is quite nice.
我不知道你怎么能...
I don't know how you can--
吃得下嗎
Eat?
不  我...
No, I'm...
很高興見你恢復食欲
glad to see you're eating.
總統女士  情勢已經無法挽救
Madam President, it's beyond repair.
到了這個地步  你明白吧
You understand that, at this point?
你失去了國會的支持
You've lost the Hill.
失去了內閣的支持
You've lost your cabinet.
失去了國家的支持
You've lost the country.
你輸了
You've lost.
你所屬的政黨也找不到理由支持你
Your own party can't even find a reason to support you.
我懇求你
I entreat you--
懇求我
You entreat me?
辭職
Resign.
你這是以副總統的身份對我說嗎
And are you speaking to me as vice president?
我以一個人的身份對你說
I'm speaking to you as a person.
就說是
Blame it on...
弗蘭西斯的死帶來的壓力  總統職務的重荷
the strain after Francis' death, the strain of the office itself.
說辭總是有  但你現在最好的結果
Language can be found, but the best you can hope for now...
就是帶著尊嚴離開
is a dignified exit.
他最令人動容之處  在于他沒法不如此
What's so moving about him is he can't help himself.
如此言行得體  充滿人性
He can't help being decent. Human.
他那光榮的缺陷
His glorious flaw.
這意味著
What this means is
他們會行動的
they're gonna go through with it.
不  馬克
No, Mark.
我哪也不去
I'm staying right where I am.
給你兩分鐘
You got two minutes.
這不是瑞秋·波斯納
That's not Rachel Posner.
是嗎
Is it?
你認識瑞秋·波斯納
You knew Rachel Posner.
應該
I mean...
算是吧
yeah, I guess.
你和她熟到可以把她名字給別人
Enough to use her name for someone else's ID?
這就是你做的生意吧
That's what you do, isn't it?
給下位客戶前一個人的名字
Kind of pay the names forward?
不是
No.
你給了瑞秋什么假名
What name did you give Rachel?
我不記得了
I don't remember.
我說真的
I don't.
你最后一次見到她是什么時候
When did you last see her?
饒了我吧
Come on.
可能幾年前吧
Couple of years ago or something.
在她上班的地方
It was where she worked.
她死了嗎
Is she dead?
-跟我沒關系  -你是不是幫兇
- I got nothing to do with that. - Did you help kill her?
我在跟你說話
I'm talking to you.
別這樣  我要找律師
Man. I want my lawyer.
你認識
Do you know...
道格·斯坦普嗎
Doug Stamper?
不認識
No.
你給了她什么假名
What name did you give her?
她叫什么名字
What was her name?
麗莎
Lisa.
-麗莎  -嗯  麗莎  凱茜
- Lisa? - Yeah. Lisa Cassie.
-麗莎·凱茜  -凱茜  麗莎
- Lisa Cassie? - Cassie, Lisa.
-對  -麗莎和凱茜
- Yeah. - Lisa and Cassie?
你回到白宮了
Back at the White House.
你住進了他的房間
You took his room.
更寬敞些
It's bigger.
你能告訴我為什么
Can you tell me why
我們非要現在在這里見面嗎
it was so important that we meet here and now?
老實說  我是希望能在白宮西樓會面的
Honestly, I was hoping we could meet in the West Wing.
我已經在這里足不出戶...
I haven't left the residence in...
我相信你還是看新聞的
Well, I'm sure you still read the news.
而且你的赦免
And your pardon...
沒有幫到我或弗蘭西斯
hasn't helped me or Francis.
我在這里感覺不舒服
I don't feel comfortable here.
不管你在這里有什么不好的回憶  道格
Whatever bad memories you may have, Doug...
有時候要花很長時間才能理解
sometimes it takes a long time to understand
是誰真正傷害了我們
who's the real source of our harm.
我沒能讓你相信我
And I have failed to make you trust me,
這太遺憾了
and that's a shame.
我相信我所了解的
I trust what I know.
你有很多敵人  他們低估了你
You have enemies, and they underestimate you.
你認為他們會怎樣攻擊我
And how do you think they'll come at me?
科爾議員對你說什么了嗎
Has Congressman Cole said anything to you?
我覺得她還活著
I think she's alive.
凱茜·杜蘭特
Cathy Durant.
我不知道她在哪里或在搞什么事  但是...
I don't know where she is or what she's up to, but...
我知道你會想知道的
I knew you'd want to know.
我想讓你知道一件事情
I want you to know something.
弗蘭西斯死在這間屋子里
Francis died in this room.
我告訴大家他死在我床上
I told everyone it was in my bed.
但其實就在這片地板上
But it was right there on the floor.
不管是誰殺了他
Whoever killed him.
我遺漏了什么嗎
Am I missing something?
殺了他的人
Whoever killed him
將得到她或他應有的下場
will get what she or he deserves.
時機決定了宇宙的形狀
Timing decided the shape of the universe.
誰說的
Who said that?
我
Me.
地獄是明白得太晚的真理
Hell is truth seen too late.
這是你說的嗎
Did you say that?
托馬斯·霍布斯
Thomas Hobbes.
厄舍
Usher...
你下注
your bet.
-我要看牌  謝謝  -別這么禮貌
- I'll check, please. - Don't be polite.
我以前和你玩過
I played with you before.
我知道你有好牌
I know you're holding.
比爾  你確定嗎
Bill, you sure?
我可以在下一手分牌給你
I can deal you in on the next hand.
-我不玩  -她真瘋了嗎
- I don't play. - Is it true she's a basket case?
或者就是一個普通的民主黨人
Or just a plain old Democrat.
我會把信準備好
So, I'll have the letter.
要看我的牌得再加一百
That's a hundred to see mine.
等時間到了  漢克
And when it comes time, Hank,
我不想最后
I don't want to end up
在參議院里  一手拿著一張紙
on the Senate floor with a piece of paper in one hand--
另一只手上只有你的蛋
And your balls in the other?
我們都是過來人
We've all been there.
別說我的蛋了
Just keep my balls out of it.
厄舍  你要讓我去拉票
Usher, you want me to whip,
卻不讓我告訴參議員們他們在為什么投票
but you don't want me to tell my senators what they're voting on.
還要不經過討論就通過
And pass without debate.
我不跟
I'm out.
至少告訴我他們會得到什么
At least tell me what they're getting.
白宮的新主人
A new resident in the White House.
總統先生
Well, Mr. President.
你是跟還是不跟
Are you in or are you out?
我跟
I call.
還有...
And...
加注500
bump you 500.
我永遠不會稱這里為敵方領地
I would never call this enemy territory.
聽起來可能有點奇怪
It might sound quaint,
但我相信共和制
but I believe in the Republic.
感謝你的到來
Well, thank you for coming.
這種媒體的攻擊
It's not sustainable.
是持續不下去的
This media onslaught.
不知你是否可以考慮叫你的狗收手
I wonder if you'd consider calling off the dogs.
就暫緩一下  幾天就行
All I'm asking for is a pause. Couple of days or so.
你恭維我了  總統女士
You flatter me, Madam President.
但我的能力也不過如此
But my reach only goes so far.
看來他們想讓你辭職
It seems they want you to resign.
是誰想
Who's they?
誰不想
Who isn't?
請原諒我的直言不諱
Pardon my bluntness.
不  我喜歡直言不諱  這樣節省時間
Oh, no, I enjoy bluntness. Saves time.
但我是否應該因身為女性而辭職
But should I resign for the high crime of being a female?
我認為有比那更深刻的原因
Oh, I think the reasoning goes deeper than that.
我認為...
I think...
這只是我個人的觀點
and this is just my perspective,
-如果你想聽的話  -請盡管說
- if you want to hear it. - Oh, please.
我們家族與你之間的爭斗
Dueling agendas between my family,
已經開始自行發展了
and, well, you, have taken on their own life.
從某種意義上說  你丈夫又不肯放過你
And in some sense, your husband just won't leave you alone,
是吧
will he?
我無法改變過去
I can't change history.
不過有時候你肯定希望自己能
I'll bet sometimes you'd like to.
你不想抹掉他嗎
Wouldn't you like to erase him?
總統女士
Madam President...
你已故的丈夫跟我媽媽說了許多事
your dead husband told my mother things.
你不想讓全世界知道的事
Things you don't want the world to know.
我覺得  一個死人的話沒什么用
A dead man's words are worthless as far as I'm concerned.
要是他所說的能被證實就不一樣了
Not when his claims can be verified.
不過有辦法讓關于某個人的記憶消失
It's possible to make the memory of a person disappear.
用數字手段
Digitally.
至少能把記憶移得遠遠的
Move them far into the background, anyways.
總是有方法的
There are ways.
算法
Algorithms.
你是個非常自信的年輕人
You're a very confident young man.
你的作為也能消失
Even your deeds can go away.
我能讓我們更容易通力合作
Now, I can make it easier for all of us to work together.
你媽媽知道你來了嗎
Does your mother know you're here?
不知道
No.
就是好奇一問  你最早的記憶是什么
Just out of curiosity, what's your first memory?
關于她的最早的記憶
Your first memory of her?
這個問題好奇怪
That's a strange question.
我就是好奇
I was just curious.
我有一張她接住我的照片
I have a photograph of her catching me.
我媽媽把我扔到空中
My mother had thrown me up into the air,
我舅舅用他的新尼康相機抓拍到了那一幕
and my uncle snapped a picture on his new Nikon camera.
她喜氣洋洋
She's beaming.
特別高興
Gleeful.
我一直珍藏著那張照片
I treasure that photo.
我記憶中的她就是這樣的
It's how I like to think of her.
幫我個忙
Do me a favor.
問問安奈特
Ask Annette--
問問你媽媽  你是從哪來的
Ask your mother where you came from.
天怎么還沒黑
It's still light out?
你真是讓人大汗淋漓
You're very dehydrating.
我知道
I know, I know.
你想談談協議
You want to talk about the deal.
你把我排除在外  簡
You excluded me, Jane.
等塵埃落定  我會滿足你的
When the dust settles, I'll give you what you want.
我沒懷疑過你的本事
Never doubted your value.
你見到我的手機了嗎
Have you seen my phone?
在衛生間
It's in the restroom.
該死
Shit.
你是不是動了我的...
Did you do something to my--
我去環保署了
I went to the EPA.
什么都沒有
There is nothing.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
有些人  混進了城里
There are people walking around this town,
穿著普通  裝成是本地人
dressed down, acting like they belong.
但我知道他們不是
But I know they don't.
你被威脅了嗎
Have you been threatened?
拜托  他們不會蠢到威脅我的
Come on, they're too smart for that.
所以他們在跟蹤你
Well, so they're following you.
但如果什么都沒有
But if there's nothing,
-那就...  -我有截圖
- then there's-- - I have screenshots...
郵件往來的截圖
of the e-mail chain.
因為他們做了錯事
'Cause it's wrong what they did.
因為我太傻了
'Cause I'm so stupid.
傻到相信在這個操蛋的世界里
So stupid to believe in doing the right thing
堅持正義
in this totally fucked up world.
其中有一封郵件是比爾·謝潑德的辦公室發的
There's an e-mail from Bill Shepherd's office in the chain.
我說過  他們早就知道
I told you. They knew.
他們早就知道會出人命
They knew somebody was gonna die.
我得走了
I gotta go.
等等
Wait.
怎么了
What?
你的手機
Your phone.
-手機怎么了  -我信不過
- What about it? - I don't trust it.
我丟掉了我的手機
I got rid of mine.
我發誓  感覺像是他們在跟蹤我的手機
I swear, it felt like they were following my phone
而不是我
and not me.
-怎么會  -我得走了
- How? - Look, I gotta go.
我會再聯系你的
I'll reach out to you.
-好嗎  -不  你說什么...
- Okay? - No. What--
她在沙特阿拉伯的某個地方
She's somewhere in Saudi Arabia.
女士  她落入敵人手中  對我們風險極大
Ma'am, she poses a significant risk in enemy hands.
你知道的
You know that.
美國不與恐怖分子談判
The United States does not negotiate with terrorists.
不用談判  特戰司令部在制定幾種行動計劃
No negotiations. Options are being drawn up at SOCOM.
但必須有行政命令才能執行
But nothing can happen without an executive order.
那...
Well, then.
等你當了總統  再發布行政命令好了
That's gonna have to happen when you're president.
簡被捕  誰的秘密都不安全
No one's secrets are safe with Jane in captivity.
你可能會比我更擔心這一點
That may be more concerning for you than it is for me.
捅了馬蜂窩  該開始推進計劃了
Kicking the hornet's nest. Time to move this thing along.
-你個自大的混蛋  -冷靜
- You arrogant little prick. - Please, just calm down.
你以為我發現不了嗎
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
你罵人的話  我可要走了
I'm not staying if there's name-calling.
我怎么罵都不過分  安妮
There's not enough names to call him, Annie.
真是蠢得清奇
Such stunning stupidity.
頭韻押得真妙  比爾舅舅
Nice alliteration, Uncle Bill.
這條毛巾都比你聰明
This towel is smarter than you.
這扇窗都比你聰明
This window is smarter than you.
這塊地毯都比你聰明
This rug is smarter than you.
-你好  賽斯  -你好  先生
- Hello, Seth. - Hello, sir.
賽斯都比你聰明
Seth is smarter than you!
我眉毛上的汗
The sweat on my brow
-都比你聰明  鄧肯  -我的天啊
- is smarter than you, Duncan. - Jesus H. Christ,
-行了吧  -因為我眉毛上的汗
- spare us. - Because sweat on my brow,
至少都清楚不能擅自去見
would have at least known not to pay an unsanctioned visit
-美國總統  -放開他
- to the President of the United States. - Get your hands off him.
我知道你不舒服  但
I know you're not feeling well, but...
這話是什么意思
Well, what the hell is that supposed to mean, anyway?
你不能這樣
You can't act like this.
我只是想幫忙  是她請我去的
You know, I was trying to help. She invited me and--
那你就去了  真他媽白癡
And you went, like a fucking idiot--
我想成為溝通橋梁
I wanted to be a bridge.
閉嘴  你們倆都閉嘴吧
Shut up, both of you, just shut up.
天啊  我們有什么沒為你做到的嗎
God, is there anything we haven't done for you?
家人之間就該如此
Well, you know, that's what people do for family.
-為彼此不惜一切  -聽著  你不該去的
- Anything. - Listen, you shouldn't have gone.
她不值得信任  我跟你說過無數次了
She can't be trusted, as I've told you a million times.
他壞了我們的時機
He jeopardized our timing.
他壞了我們對她下手的時機
He jeopardized our timing with her!
我再也受不了男人吵架了
I can't stand the sound of male arguing anymore.
她讓我問你件事
You know, she told me to ask you something.
她讓我問你我從哪來的
She told me to ask you where I came from.
賽斯  賽斯
Seth. Seth!
16周
Sixteen weeks.
她跟丈夫懷的那個孩子
The one from the pregnancy with her husband.
安妮  這的確不是好主意
Annie, I do think it'd be a mistake.
賽斯  確認下
Seth, confirm it.
-沒錯  16周  -她丈夫告訴我的
- That's right. Sixteen weeks. - Her husband told me.
但你不知道事態會怎樣發展  是吧
But you don't know how it's gonna play. Okay?
可能事與愿違  讓人們同情她
It could backfire. Get her sympathy.
-誰會等到16周  -我們無法控制輿論發展
- Who waits 16 weeks? - The narrative can't be controlled--
什么人會這么做  人們會談論這個
What kind of person, that's what people will be talking about.
給馬克打電話  立刻開始
Let's get Mark on the phone. We start this now.
我們就叫她麗薩
Only "Lisa" is what we called her.
她在中心市場的同事
The lady at Central Market, where she worked,
說你好幾次去找過她
said you stopped by a few times asking for her.
她欠我們錢  但
She owed us some money, but...
她死了嗎
She dead?
不知道
I don't know.
里面沒多少東西
There's not much in there.
幾封信
Some letters.
紙片  清單  還有
Scraps and lists and...
照片
Picture.
都不值錢
Nothing, really.
我們國家遇到了問題
Our country has a problem right now.
總統
The president,
她無視高級顧問的建議
she has ignored the advice of her senior advisers,
那都是有學問  有作戰經驗的人
people who have studied and fought battles.
她的精神狀態讓我們陷入更糟的...
Her state of mind has left us in a weakened...
我們得守住陣線
We need to hold the line
直到國家回到正軌
till our country gets back on course.
這段視頻令人震驚
That is a truly stunning video.
對于國防部長對總統的批評
What is your reaction to the secretary of defense's critique
你怎么看
of this president?
國防部長漢納是四星海軍陸戰隊將軍
Secretary Defense Hanna is a four-star Marine General
服役四十多年了
with over 40 years of service to this country.
我理解他的失望
I understand his frustration.
據稱馬克·厄舍掌握著白宮實權
Is there any truth to the idea that Mark Usher
就像小布什的迪克·切尼  是真的嗎
is the Dick Cheney of this White House?
不  迪克·切尼只有一個
No, there is only one Dick Cheney.
-這話不假  -馬克·厄舍
- Okay, fair enough. - Mark Usher is
就是這屆政府的馬克·厄舍
the Mark Usher of this White House.
那你怎么定位現任副總統的角色
So, how would you characterize the vice president's role?
副總統受到了內閣的全力支持
The vice president has the full support of the entire cabinet.
那總統呢
And the president?
總統能為自己說話
Well, the president speaks for herself.
你的意思是國防部長
Are you suggesting that the Secretary of Defense
不是唯一不滿總統的人嗎
is not the only one who's frustrated with this president?
勞倫斯  這座城市充斥著流言蜚語
You know, Lawrence, this town feeds off of rumor and gossip
-這只會適得其反  -吃點嗎
- and it's counter-productive. - Raha?
這是分散注意力  我不來這套
It's a distraction. I don't work that way.
你不來這套  那你來哪套
You don't work that way. How do you work?
-你在現任總統那里來哪套  -你有電話
- How do you work with this president? - You have a call.
是你的總統
It's your president.
這屆政府無法正常運轉了嗎
Is this a dysfunctional administration?
我與總統的關系
My relationship with this...
克萊爾
Claire.
簡  我只想知道
Jane, I just need to know
他們到底什么時候動手
exactly when they're going to pull the trigger.
你不想回家嗎
Don't you want to come home?
你倒是挺開心的樣子
You look like you're having fun.
我認為你們是有真情的
I see real affection there.
當然外界也有關于我和湯姆的謠言
And, listen, there were rumors about Tom and me, of course,
但全都不是真的
but nothing to them.
他對我來說像個弟弟
He was like a brother to me.
總能安慰我
So comforting.
也正是因此  這才更讓人難過
Which is what makes this all the more difficult.
真相是  凱爾茜
The truth is, Kelsey...
是俄羅斯人殺了湯姆
the Russians killed Tom...
馬克·厄舍幫忙掩蓋了事實
and Mark Usher covered it up.
我將竭盡所能讓他為此事負責
Now, I'm doing my best to hold him accountable,
但我需要你的幫助
but I need your help.
我要你告訴聯調局
I need you to tell the FBI
你和湯姆的關系
about your relationship with Tom.
-總統女士  我...  -我懂  沒關系的
- Madam President, I-- - I know. It's fine.
說你倆當時在約會
You just say you were dating.
在談戀愛
You were in love.
有次在私下里
And in a private moment,
他向你透露了他懷疑
he told you about his suspicions regarding
馬克·厄舍與俄羅斯串謀
Mark Usher and his collusion with Russia.
而你最后一次見到他時
And the last time you saw him,
他正要去副總統的宅邸
he was on his way to the vice president's home
與他對峙
to confront him.
我不會讓副總統逍遙法外的
I'm not going to let the vice president get away with this.
你和我身為女人
You and I, as women,
我們必須反擊
we have to fight back.
我需要你和我并肩作戰
I need you by my side.
在我們送出信之前
And before we transmit the letter,
我想請所有人低下頭
I'd like to suggest we all take a moment to bow our heads
為我們偉大的祖國祈禱
and pray for this great nation.
能把信遞給我嗎
Could you pass me that letter?
還有  把你們的東西收好
And gather all of your things.
在場所有內閣成員
Every single cabinet member in this room
都可以走了
is dismissed.
你們都被解雇了
You're all fired.
送他們出去
Escort them out.
你知道
You know,
我從沒想過你是
I never took you for someone
想入主白宮的人
who wanted to get himself into the Oval.
不過是個四年的飯碗  幸運的話是八年
All it is, is a four year job, eight if you're lucky.
你在哪
Where are you?
什么
What?
好  我馬上回來
All right. I'm on my way back.
要是她干預簽署  那就是妨礙司法
Listen, if she prevented the signing, that's obstruction.
可能會使她遭彈劾
And likely, it's impeachable.
聽見了嗎
You hear me?
細節仍在傳來
Details are still coming in.
但是據了解  今天聯調局
But we're being told there are reports that the FBI...
-馬克  -收到證據顯示
- Mark. - ...has today been provided evidence...
-去看電視  -馬克·厄舍與俄國官員
- Get to a television. - ...that Mark Usher had quote...
-或是電腦  -有"情節重大
- Or a computer. - ..."significant and ongoing...
或是打開電臺
Or a goddamn radio.
且仍在持續的私下聯系"
...contact outside the logs with Russian officials."
這促成了總統近期所簽署的
This leading up to and during the president's
反應兩極化的敘利亞和平協議
recent polarizing Syrian peace deal.
聯調局會調查此事
The FBI's expected to look into the matter,
但他們尚未宣布是否會啟動
but has yet to announce whether or not they are opening
正式調查
an official investigation.
如果屬實  這將是本屆多災多難的政府
If so, this could be a catastrophic setback
遭遇的又一災難性挫敗
for an already-beleaguered administration.
在我們開始之前  我想給你一個請辭的機會
Before we begin, I'd like to offer you the chance to resign.
那我就不打擾你了
I'll leave you to it then.
我和俄羅斯從沒有過非正式聯系  從來沒有
I never had any contact with any Russians outside the logs. None.
1991年夏天你曾在副外交部長左爾金位于
You vacationed at Deputy Foreign Minister Zorkin's family dacha
-黑海的鄉間別墅度假  -二十年前的事了
- on the Black Sea in summer 1991. - That was 20 years ago.
我們回溯一下  從凱爾茜·斯圖爾特小姐的證詞
Let's work backwards, start with questions that have arisen
引起的疑問開始
after Ms. Kelsey Stewart's deposition.
誰
Who?
我們定位她的手機在貝爾波特的一家酒水店
We located her phone in a liquor store in Bellport.
她知道應用的事了
She knows about the app.
應該是吧
We should assume so.
你告訴我舅舅了嗎
Have you told my uncle yet?
我聯系不上他
I can't reach him.
我也聯系不上你母親
I can't reach your mother, either.
我們已經派人追蹤那位記者
We have some men tracking the journalist.
我們還不知道她是否取得了任何證據
But we don't even know if she has her hands on anything yet.
-謝潑德先生的包裹  -謝謝
- Package for Mr. Shepherd. - Oh, thank you.
寫著是給你的
This is addressed to you.
請讓我獨處一會兒
Leave me alone, please.
我是凱瑟琳·杜蘭特
My name is Catherine Durant.
今天是2017年7月18日  星期二
Today is Tuesday, July 18, 2017.
時間是
And the time...
晚上8點37分
8:37 p.m.
在我開始之前  我想說
Now, before I begin, let me just say...
歷史必將帶給
that every punishment
克萊爾·安德伍德的所有懲罰
that history will surely visit upon Claire Underwood
都是她罪有應得
will be exactly what she deserves.
我萬分懊悔當初接受了她丈夫提供的
I rue the day that I accepted her husband's offer
國務卿一職
of secretary of state.
好了
Now, then...
我發誓我接下來絕無虛言
I hereby swear that everything I'm about to say is the truth.
她丈夫六小時前失蹤了
Her husband has disappeared, as of six hours ago.
-你還想聽嗎  -不了
- Do you want to hear any more? - No.
我知道后面是什么
I know the rest.
你覺得是俄羅斯人幫他們逃掉的嗎
Do you think the Russians got them out?
不  我能肯定是
Uh, no, I'm sure of it.
你覺得她發給其他人了嗎
Do you think she sent it to anyone else?
發了我們早就知道了
We would know about it by now.
我讓納森候命于你
I've asked Nathan to be available to you.
我知道你倆合作很默契
I know how well you two work with one another.
我們會找到她的
We'll find her.
道格  我還沒忘
And, Doug, I haven't forgotten
我們對彼此的承諾
about the promise we made to each other.
但愿你也沒有
I hope you haven't.
我剛從新墨西哥州回來
I just got back from New Mexico.
你把瑞秋怎么了  還是把凱茜怎么了
What did you do with Rachel? Or is it Cassie?
我離你只有五分鐘路程
I'm five minutes away.
掛了電話
Hang up the phone.
-道格  -掛掉
- Doug-- - Hang it up
不然我再不會聯系你
or you'll never hear from me again.
我去找你
I'll come to you.
納森
Nathan,
你還在聽嗎
are you still listening?
你相信她會保護你就太傻了
You're a fool to think she'll protect you.
這似乎挺合適  我回來工作后
Seems fitting, somehow, that you're the first
第一個見的人就是你
person I meet with after I've returned to work.
真是好輪回啊
There's something very full circle about it.
你跟你兒子談過咯
So, you've talked to your son.
準確說那不是你兒子
Or rather, not your son.
你知道那時候胎兒有多大了嗎
Do you know how developed a fetus is by then?
16周
Sixteen weeks is...
那可是成型的胎兒
beyond the beyond.
16周的胎兒有這么大了
That is what 16 weeks looks like.
這畫面在我腦海中揮之不去
That is what I can't get out of my head.
我在學梅樂蒂·科魯茲說話呢
I'm quoting Melody Cruz here, by the way.
她剛錄好視頻  明天就放
She just taped her segment, due to run tomorrow.
還有道具增強表現力
Visual aids and everything.
美國人民會首次聽到
For the first time ever, Americans will hear the story
膝下無子的總統
of a childless president...
在婚后
who had an abortion,
做了流產
while married,
打掉了16周的胎兒
at 16 weeks.
我就想看看你的表情
I wanted to see your face.
我想看你意識到弗蘭克的背叛
I wanted to see Frank's betrayal register.
現在誰都管不住自己的嘴
Nobody can keep their mouths shut these days.
秘密都帶進墳墓了還能被挖出來
Not even to-the-death secrets are safe.
真可恥
It's shameful.
但說實話  哪樣更痛苦
But honestly, what's worse?
他泄露了你的秘密
That he betrayed your secret
還是你等到16周才墮胎
or that you waited until 16 weeks?
你和你的黨派
You and your party.
就一副道貌岸然的樣子
Your moral rectitude, how convenient.
你自己的話你一個字也不信  安奈特
You don't even believe half of what you say, Annette.
放吧
Run it.
科魯茲的報道
Cruz's piece.
放吧
Run it.
然后回去
And then go home
跟鄧肯說說他怎么來的
and talk to Duncan about the beginning of life.
你走之前
But actually before you go,
我想給你看樣東西  來
I want to show you something. Come with me.
見過我的新內閣
Meet my new cabinet.
我就想看看你的表情
I just wanted to see your face.
謝謝大家臨危受命
Thank you all for assembling at such short notice.
我想感謝各位的奉獻精神
And I want to thank you for your willingness to serve.
我很期待能共同建立一個新美國
I am looking forward to building a new America together
我們就從今天開始
and our work begins today.
現在  請你們
Now, if you could all
將左手放在自己面前的《憲法》上
place your left hand on the Constitution in front of you.
跟我念
And repeat after me:
本人莊嚴宣誓
I do solemnly swear
下手絕不留情
to take no prisoners.
今年6月第一夫人梅蘭妮因腎病緊急入院做了手術
根據病情判斷  媒體以為術后三五天她就會重回公眾視野
但是沒想到梅蘭妮一直玩失蹤  長達25天沒在媒體前露面
第一夫人玩失蹤引發媒體各種猜測  有的說她乘機整容
有的說她跟老公特朗普鬧翻離宮出走...
不過25天后  她再次出現在公共場合  所有謠言都不攻自破
不過白宮也一直沒有解釋為什么第一夫人需要這么長時間閉門養病
憲法第25修正案主要規定當總統和副總統職位出現空缺時
應怎樣啟動繼任程序  歷史上因總統副總統辭職
總統體檢麻醉等原因  共啟用過六次
本集中由副總統和內閣啟動繼任程序的第四條款  歷史上從未被使用過
特朗普上任后  他的政敵和媒體
一直對他的施政能力和各種言論進行猛烈攻擊
一些人曾在電視訪談中稱特朗普性情乖張  像瘋了一樣
精神狀態不適合履行總統職務  應該啟動第25修正案
18年9月21日  《紐約時報》爆料稱  司法部副部長羅森斯坦
曾私下建議啟用第25修正案  把特朗普從總統位置上趕下來
并表示自己可以暗中配戴竊聽裝置進入總統辦公室
偷錄特朗普講話  以證明總統無法控制白宮局勢
羅森斯坦本人堅決否認《紐約時報》的報道
但據說特朗普看了報道后一度想要炒掉羅森斯坦  但是后來回轉心意
在空軍一號上同羅森斯坦面對面交談后  決定不去動他
羅森斯坦是負責通俄門調查的最高級官員
如果特朗普把他炒掉  可能會引發"總統干預司法"的危機